sympli.io 2018-09-25

# Sympli: Bring digital products to life faster and easier.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By using or accessing the Service, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree to be bound to all the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, and the "Terms and Conditions” or other customer agreement between you and Sympli that is applicable to the particular Service you are using or accessing (collectively, "User Agreements”).

If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy and the applicable User Agreement, please exit and do not use or access the Service.

Your privacy is important to us, so please review the information below regarding our practices and policies.

## Introduction

This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) sets forth the privacy practices of Sympli, LLC and its current and future Sympli Affiliates (collectively, “Sympli”) for all Sympli software and applications (including, without limitation, mobile software and applications) (collectively, the “Software”); the Sympli websites located at sympli.io and any other Sympli websites or services that link to this Privacy Policy, (collectively, the “Websites”); and all other Sympli products or services provided or otherwise made accessible on or through the Software or the Websites or that otherwise link to or reference this Privacy Policy. The Software, the Websites, and any other Sympli products or services that link or refer to this Privacy Policy are collectively referred to as the “Service.” This Privacy Policy describes how Sympli collects, discloses, stores, transfers, and uses information that could individually identify our users (“Personal Data”) in connection with our Service. Sympli is subject to investigatory and enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties, as explained in more detail below. In this Privacy Policy, "we," “us,” “our,” and other similar references mean Sympli, “you” and “your” and other similar references mean any user of the Service, and “Sympli Affiliates” means any parent, subsidiary, member, officer, director, employee, agent, or contractor of Sympli or any entity under common control with Sympli.

This policy applies (i) immediately to new users who use or access the Service on or after the Effective Date and (ii) on the Effective Date to users who use or access the Service before the Effective Date.

Please contact us if you have any questions or comments about our privacy practices. You can reach us online at privacy@sympli.io or by mail at the address listed in the "Questions Regarding Your Personal Data" section below.

## Personal Data Storage

The Service is hosted and operated in the United States (“U.S.”), with development, support and maintenance operations in other countries through both Sympli and its service providers. If you do not reside in the U.S., laws in the U.S. may differ from the laws where you reside. By using the Service, you acknowledge that any Personal Data about you, regardless of whether provided by you or obtained from a third party, is being provided to Sympli in the U.S. and will be hosted on U.S. servers, and you authorize Sympli to transfer, store, host and process your information to and in the U.S., and possibly other countries. You hereby consent to transfer of your data to the U.S. pursuant to either, at Sympli’s discretion, the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework, the details of which are further set forth below, or the standard data protection clauses promulgated by the EC, a copy of which can be obtained at https://eur-lex.europa.eu/legal-content/EN/TXT/?uri=celex%3A32010D0087.

##### EU Personal Data

If you are located in the EU, United Kingdom, Lichtenstein, Norway, or Iceland, you may have additional rights under the EU General Data Protection Regulation (the "GDPR") related to your Personal Data, as further described below. Sympli will be the controller of your Personal Data processed in connection with the Service, unless you access the Service through an enterprise account, or other Sympli account that is controlled by a third party (e.g. your employer).

##### EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Participation & Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Participation

Sympli complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States. Sympli has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/.

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Sympli commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact Sympli at privacy@sympli.io.

Sympli has further committed to cooperate with the panel established by the EU data protection authorities (DPAs) and the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner (FDPIC) with regard to unresolved Privacy Shield complaints concerning data transferred from the EU and Switzerland.

## Types of Personal Data We Collect

Sympli collects Personal Data about you when you provide it directly to us, when third parties such as our business partners (e.g. companies with whom we integrate our Service), service providers (such as our advertising service providers) provide us with Personal Data about you, or when Personal Data about you is automatically collected in connection with your use of our Service. We collect the following Personal Data from you in connection with the Service:

  1. Contact Information: information used to identify or contact you, which may include first name, last name, title, physical address, telephone number, email address, and Twitter handle. 
  2. Financial Account Information: information you provide in connection with your purchase of the Service (or a purchase made through the Service), including credit card number, credit card expiration date, credit card verification code, bank account number, bank account title, bank name, branch location, and routing number. You must only provide us with Financial Account Information for accounts and credit cards that you have the lawful right to access. 
  3. Transaction Information: information related to transactions you conduct on the Service, including interactions with the Service, registrations for special events or webinars, customer support interactions, and other similar transactions.
  4. User Account Information: information that identifies you to the Service, such as your user name, email address, password, and IP address.
  5. User Content: Personal Data included in content, images, comments, and other content, information, and materials that you post to or through the Service.
  6. Important Note: Users of our Services should not use actual or "live" Personal Data or other sensitive data (e.g. real health information, financial information, or other information) when sharing, reviewing, and using designs through our Services. Sympli recommends following industry best practices of using “dummy data” that does not refer to actual people, financial accounts, etc. while sharing, reviewing, and using your designs and prototypes.
  7. Partner Information: information that our business partners share with us.
  8. Log Data: information automatically recorded regarding usages of the Service, such as IP addresses, device and browser type, operating system, the pages or features of our Website or Service to which a user browsed, the time spent on those pages or features, the frequency with which the Service is used by a user, search terms used by a user, the links on the Service that a user clicked on or used, and other statistics.

We also collect usage and performance information that is not Personal Data or that we aggregate or de-identify so that it no longer personally identifies an individual. We also associate some data that is not Personal Data with Personal Data.

## How we Collect Personal Data

We collect Personal Data when a user (i) creates an account (a "User Account"); (ii) logs into the Service; (iii) interacts with the Service; (iv) uploads or generates User Content; (v) communicates with us; and (vi) responds to a communication or interaction from us. Some of the methods and tools we use to collect Personal Data are:

  * Unique Identifiers: We use unique identifiers such as cookies, email or your pseudonymized customer ID to track individual usage behavior on our Service, such as the length of time spent on a particular page and the pages viewed during a particular log-in period. Unique identifiers collect information about a user’s use of our Service on an individual basis.
  * Mobile Device Identifiers: Mobile device identifiers are identifiers stored on your mobile device that track certain data and activities occurring on or through your device. Mobile device identifiers enable collection of Personal Data (such as media access controls) as well as non-personally identifiable information (such as usage and traffic data).
  * Cookies, Web Beacons, and Other Tracking Tools: We and our third party service providers collect information about you, your device, and your use of the Service through cookies (small text files that are saved by your browser when you access our Service), clear gifs (a.k.a. web beacons/web bugs) ("Web Beacons"), and other tracking tools and technological methods (collectively, “Tracking Tools”). Tracking Tools collect information such as computer or device operating system type, IP address, browser type, browser language, mobile device ID, device hardware type, the website or application visited or used before or after accessing our Service, the parts of the Service accessed, the length of time spent on a page or using a feature, and access times for a webpage or feature. These Tracking Tools help us learn more about our users and analyze how users use the Service, such as how often users visit our Service, what features they use, what pages they visit, what emails they open, and what other sites or applications they used prior to and after visiting the Service.
  * Social Media Widgets: Some parts of our Service may include social media features, such as the Facebook "like" button, and widgets, such as the “share this” button. These social media features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Service. When you use these tools, the party that provides the tool, the third party that operates the social media services, and/or we may receive Personal Data about you. By using these tools, you acknowledge that some information, including Personal Data, from your social media services will be transmitted to us, and that information is therefore is covered by this Privacy Policy, and some information, including Personal Data, may be shared with the third party services, and that information is therefore governed by their privacy policies.
  * Third Party Sources: We may use third-party services, such as open search tools and social networks, to obtain information about you (such as your name or company) and to enrich your personal information by obtaining publicly available information about you, such as your job title, employment history and contact information.
  * Online Behavioral Advertising: Some of our advertising ("Behavioral Advertising") involves using Tracking Tools to collect information about a user’s online activities over time and across non-affiliated websites and applications and providing ads to the user based the user’s interests (as inferred from the user’s online activity) or use of our Service. Behavioral Advertising may appear on our Service or on other websites or services. We work with third parties to provide Behavioral Advertising, such as advertising networks, data exchanges, traffic measurement service providers, marketing analytics service providers, and other third-party service providers (collectively, “Advertising Service Providers”). Advertising Service Providers perform services such as facilitating targeting of advertisements and measuring and analyzing advertising effectiveness on the Service (collectively, all such services, “Targeting Services”). Targeting Services help us display Behavioral Advertising, prevent you from seeing repeated ads, and enable us to research the usefulness of ads. You have the option to opt out of Behavioral Advertising. For more information, see the section below titled “Opting Out of Behavioral Advertising and Tracking Tools.”

## Use of Personal Data

Sympli uses Personal Data to: (i) provide, administer, and improve our Service; (ii) better understand your needs and interests; (iii) fulfill requests you make; (iv) personalize your experience; (v) provide Service announcements; (vi) provide you with information and offers from Sympli, Sympli Affiliates, and our business partners; (vii) protect, investigate, and deter against fraudulent, harmful, unauthorized, or illegal activity and (viii) comply with legal obligations.

For example, we use Personal Data to:

  * Operate and improve the Service
  * Learn more about our users and their internet behaviors
  * Target offers to users
  * Facilitate communications among and between users and the public in general
  * Evaluate eligibility of customers for certain offers, products, or services
  * Evaluate the types of offers, products, or services that may be of interest to users
  * Provide user support
  * Communicate with users regarding support, security, technical issues, commerce, marketing, and transactions
  * Facilitate marketing, advertising, surveys, contests, sweepstakes, and promotions
  * Administer the Service, User Accounts, and transactions with respect to User Accounts
  * Enforce our contracts, administering and carrying out our obligations under contracts, and complying with the law
  * Publish aggregated data about usage trends, which may be derived from Personal Data
  * Complete corporate transactions such as mergers, sales of assets, or bankruptcies

## Processing Basis

We will only use your Personal Data if we have a lawful basis for doing so. Lawful bases for processing include consent, contractual necessity, and our "legitimate interests" or the legitimate interest of others, as further described below.

  * Contractual Necessity: We may process Personal Data in order to perform under our User Agreement with you and to provide you with the Service. We process the following categories of Personal Data where failure to provide such data will result in your inability to use some or all portions of the Service:

    * Contact Information
    * User Account Information
    * Financial Account Information
    * Transaction Information
    * User Content
  * Legitimate Interest: We process the following categories of Personal Data when we believe doing so furthers the legitimate interest of us or third parties:

    * Contact Information
    * Financial Account Information
    * User Account Information
    * Transaction Information
    * User Content
    * Partner Information
    * Log Data

Examples of these legitimate interests include:

  *     * Operation and improvement of our business, products, and services

    * Marketing of our products and services

    * Provision of customer support

    * Protection from fraud or security threats

    * Compliance with legal obligations

    * Completion of corporate transactions

  * Consent: In some cases, we process Personal Data based on the consent you expressly grant to us at the time we collect such data. When we process Personal Data based on your consent, it will be expressly indicated to you at the point and time of collection.
  * Other Processing Grounds: From time to time we may also need to process Personal Data to comply with a legal obligation, if it is necessary to protect the vital interests of you or other data subjects, or if it is necessary for a task carried out in the public interest.

## Sharing of Personal Data

We may share Personal Data with third parties who work on our behalf and provide us with services related to or in support of the Service, including vendors, third party service providers, and other agents. These third parties may include, but are not limited to:

  * Third parties who act for us or provide services for us, such as billing and credit card payment processing, maintenance, sales, marketing, administration, support, data enrichment, hosting, and database management services
  * Outside professional advisors (such as lawyers and accountants) for purposes related to the operation of our business such as auditing, compliance, and corporate governance
  * Sympli Affiliates, including persons or entities that acquire some or all of Sympli or our assets
  * Co-sponsors and presenters of webinars and events that you attend

We also may share Personal Data with third party service providers and agents when necessary to complete a transaction initiated or authorized by you or provide you with a product or service you have requested. In addition to those set forth above, these parties also include:

  * Other users (when you use a "share link" to post information publicly, share or comment on content, or as otherwise necessary to effect a transaction initiated or authorized by you through the Service)
  * Social media services (if you interact with them through your use of the Service)
  * Third party business partners who you access through the Service
  * Other parties authorized by you
  * The owner and administrator(s) of the Service account that you use, or of the email address that you used to register with the Service (see "Third Party Enterprise Accounts" immediately below).

We share Personal Data with presenters, sponsors, or other conference participants or organizers if you register for or attend a conference in which we are involved. We also share Personal Data when we believe we are required to do so, such as to:

  * Comply with applicable law or respond to valid legal process, including from law enforcement or other government agencies
  * Protect us, our business or our users, or third parties, for example to enforce our service, prevent spam or other unwanted communications and investigate or protect against fraud
  * Maintain the security of our products and services

We also share information with third parties when you have given us consent to do so.

To the extent provided by the Privacy Shield Principles, Sympli remains responsible and liable under the Privacy Shield Principles if a third-party that it engages to process personal information on its behalf does so in a manner inconsistent with the Privacy Shield Principles, unless Sympli proves that it is not responsible for the matter giving rise to the damage.

## Third Party Enterprise Accounts

If you register for the Service using an email address that we recognize to be either a part of a third-party enterprise account for the Service (an "Enterprise Account") or a potential enterprise Service purchaser (for example, your employer’s) (each, an “Organization”), we may provide your name and email address to the Organization and their administrator. In some cases, we will also consolidate your account(s) with the accounts of the Organization and we provide your Organization and their administrator with access to your User Account information and User Content. This may happen when the Organization’s account is established after you register for your individual User Account. We make these transfers to allow users who are part of a larger organization to take advantage of the special features and security enjoyed by our enterprise Account holders, and in order to help you and your organization comply with its internal security and email usage obligations. Please note that all accounts for the Service, and all applicable sub-accounts (which may include your User Account), are controlled by the account administrator. In certain cases (e.g. when we are aggregating all of the accounts under a current or potential Enterprise Account), we will provide you with the ability to opt-out of consolidation with an Organization’s Account (typically by changing the email address on your account to a non-Organization email address).

Additionally, when an Organization creates an Account, we may notify any individuals already using the Services under an email address with the same company domain as yours so that they can be migrated to your enterprise Account.

## Data Transfers

Sympli may sell, transfer, or otherwise share some or all of its business or assets, including your Personal Data, in connection with a business deal (or the evaluation of a potential business deal) such as a merger, consolidation, acquisition, reorganization, or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and that any acquirer or successor of Sympli or its assets may continue to use your Personal Data as set forth in this Privacy Policy. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Website or Service of any change in ownership or resulting change in uses of your Personal Data, as well as any choices you may have regarding your Personal Data. Similarly, if you access the Service as part of a third party Enterprise Account, the individual or entity controlling the Enterprise Account may transfer or otherwise share the account (including your User Account, User Content, and Personal Data) to an acquirer of some or all of its assets in connection with the migration to an Organization’s account, or a business deal (or the evaluation of a potential business deal) such as a merger, consolidation, acquisition, reorganization, or sale of assets, or in the event of bankruptcy.

## Privacy Options

Opting Out of Behavioral Advertising and Tracking Tools

You can opt-out of certain Behavioral Advertising activities by doing one or more of the following. Please note that you will need to opt-out of each browser and device for which you desire to apply these opt-out features.

  * Service Provider Opt Out: You can opt-out directly from some Advertising Service Providers and providers of Tracking Tools by using their opt-out tools. Some of these service providers, and links to their opt-out tools, are: 
    * Google Analytics: with a privacy policy at http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/ and opt out at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
  * Industry Opt Out Tools: Some Advertising Service Providers or providers of Tracking Tools may participate in the Network Advertising Initiative's (NAI) Opt-Out Tool (http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) and/or the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) Consumer Choice Page (http://www.aboutads.info/choices/), and you can opt-out of certain services and learn more about your choices by visiting the links included there. Users in the EU can visit http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/ for more information about your choices and to opt out of participating service providers.
  * Web Browser Controls: You can prevent the use of certain Tracking Tools, such as cookies, on a device-by-device basis using the controls in your web browser. These controls can be found in the Preferences (or similar) menu for your browser, or as otherwise directed by your browser’s support feature. Through your web browser, you may be able to: 
    * Delete existing Tracking Tools
    * Disable future Tracking Tools
    * Set your browser to provide you with a warning each time a cookie or certain other Tracking Tools are being set
  * Do Not Track: Your browser may offer you a "Do Not Track" option, which allows you to signal to operators of websites and web applications and services (including behavioral advertising services) that you do not wish such operators to track certain of your online activities over time and across different websites. The Service does not support Do Not Track requests at this time, which means that we may collect information about your online activity both while you are using the Service and after you leave our Service.
  * Opting-out of Behavioral Advertising does not mean that you will no longer receive online ads. It only means that such ads will no longer be tailored to your specific viewing habits or interests. You may continue to see ads on and about the Service.
  * Emails: We will give you the ability to opt-out of marketing-related emails by clicking on a link at the bottom of each such email. You cannot opt-out of receiving certain non-marketing emails regarding the Service.
  * Information Shared with Third Parties: Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy, you will be notified when your Personal Data may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information. To the extent permitted or required by applicable law, you can opt-out of having your information shared with a third party that is not our agent, by contacting us at privacy@sympli.io. However, please note that opting-out of information sharing or collection may affect your ability to use some features of the Service.

## Security

The security of your information is a serious issue and we are committed to protecting the information we receive from you. We use commercially reasonable security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of your information under our control based on the type of Personal Data and applicable processing activity, such as data encryption in transit, data encryption at rest (for customers that elect to purchase our "private cloud" solution), pseudonymization, and enforcement of least privilege and need-to-know principles.

To the extent the Service requires you to provide any Financial Account Information, such as when you purchase subscriptions to the Service, that information will be collected and processed by third-party PCI-compliant service providers. We do not store Financial Account Information transmitted through the Service, provided that we do store (or our payment processor on our behalf will store) just the last four digits of your credit card number, if you provide this to us, to comply with credit card processing requirements of authorizations, charges and chargebacks.

## Data Retention

We retain Personal Data about you for as long as you have an open account with us or as otherwise necessary to provide you with the Service, and thereafter as set forth in our Service agreement with you (typically 30 days after termination of the Service, or sooner upon request (except as required by law)). In some cases we retain Personal Data for longer, if doing so is necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes or collect fees owed, or is otherwise permitted or required by applicable law, rule, or regulation. Upon disposal, we will destroy or render unreadable any such Personal Data. Afterwards, we retain some information in a depersonalized or aggregated form but not in a way that would identify you personally.

## Third Party Sites

This Privacy Policy applies only to the Service. It does not apply to products, services, or sites that are provided by or operated by third parties, even if such products, services or sites are linked or redirected to or from the Service ("Third Party Sites"), regardless of whether or not such link or redirection is authorized by Sympli. Third Party Sites may have their own policies regarding privacy, or no policy at all. The fact that we link to a Third Party Site is not an endorsement, authorization, or representation that we are affiliated with that third party. Sympli is not responsible for Third Party Sites, and you use them at your own risk. We encourage you to read the privacy policies and the Third Party Sites that you visit or use.

The Service contains areas where you may be able to publicly post information, communicate with others, submit media content, and/or review goods, services, or vendors, such as discussion boards or blogs. Any information, including Personal Data that you post there, will be public and can be viewed by the public at large, and therefore anyone who accesses such postings will have the ability to read, collect, and further disseminate such information. We have no control over, and take no responsibility for, the use, storage, or dissemination of information posted or otherwise made available on such portions of the Service. By posting Personal Data online in public forums, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties.

## Your Rights Regarding Personal Data

##### Accessing, Correcting, and Deleting Your Personal Data and Other Data Subject Rights

You have certain rights with respect to your Personal Data, and we want to help you review and update your information to ensure it is accurate and up-to-date. We may limit or reject your request in certain cases, such as if it is frivolous or extremely impractical, if it jeopardizes the rights of others, if it is not required by law, or if the burden or expense of providing access would be disproportionate to the risks to your privacy in the case in question. In some cases, we may also need you to provide us with additional information, which may include Personal Data, to verify your identity and the nature of your request. We will take reasonable steps to respond to all requests within 30 days.

If you are an Sympli Account holder, you can accomplish most of the following by logging into your User Account or, for those using Enterprise Accounts, by contacting your account administrator. You can also contact us directly at privacy@sympli.io if you have any additional requests or questions regarding:

  * Access: You can request more information about the Personal Data we hold about you and request a copy of such Personal Data. 
  * Correction: If you believe that any Personal Data we are holding about you is incorrect or incomplete, you can request that we correct or supplement such data.
  * Deletion: You can request that we erase some or all of your Personal Data from our systems. Please note that if you request the deletion of information required to provide the Service to you, your User Account will be deactivated and you will lose access to the Service.
  * Portability: You can ask for a copy of your Personal Data in a machine-readable format. You can also request that we transmit the data to another controller where technically feasible.
  * Withdrawal of Consent: If we are processing your Personal Data based on your consent (as indicated at the time of collection of such data), you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. Please note, however, that if you exercise this right, you may have to then provide express consent on a case-by-case basis for the use or disclosure of certain of your Personal Data, if such use or disclosure is necessary to enable you to utilize some or all of our Service.
  * Objection: You can contact us to let us know that you object to the further use or disclosure of your Personal Data for certain purposes, such as for marketing purposes.
  * Restriction of Processing: You can ask us to restrict further processing of your Personal Data.

You also have the right to lodge a complaint about Sympli’s practices with respect to your Personal Data with the supervisory authority of your country or EU Member State.

##### Closing Your Account

You may close an account, and upon termination of your User Account, we will take reasonable steps to provide, modify, or delete your Personal Data as soon as is practicable. However, Sympli may nevertheless retain your Personal Data to protect the business interests of Sympli, Sympli Affiliates, vendors, and other users, and some information may remain in archived/backup copies for our records or as otherwise required by law. Those interests include without limitation the completion of transactions, maintaining records for financial reporting purposes, complying with our legal obligations, resolving disputes, and enforcing agreements.

##### California Privacy Rights

Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California can obtain certain information about the types of Personal Data that companies with whom they have an established business relationship have shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year. In particular, the law provides that companies must inform consumers about the categories of Personal Data that have been shared with third parties, the names and addresses of those third parties, and examples of the types of services or products marketed by those third parties. To request a copy of the information disclosure provided by Sympli pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, please contact as set forth above.

## Enforcement & Recourse

We take our privacy commitments very seriously. We will conduct internal audits of our compliance with this Privacy Policy, and work to ensure that our employees and service providers also adhere to the Privacy Policy. If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy related to the Service, please send us a detailed message to privacy@sympli.io, and we will try to resolve your concerns. We also commit to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of Personal Data transferred from the EU to the U.S. in compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles where applicable. 

You may have the option to select binding arbitration under the Privacy Shield Panel for the resolution of your complaint under certain circumstances. For further information, to learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework, and to view Sympli’s certification, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov.

## Privacy Policy Changes

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, you will be notified via email (if you have an account where we have your contact information) or otherwise in some manner through the Service that we deem reasonably likely to reach you (which may include posting a new privacy policy on our Website—or a specific announcement on this page or on our blog). Any modifications to this Privacy Policy will be effective upon our posting of the new terms and/or upon implementation of the new changes on the Service (or as otherwise indicated at the time of posting) or on the Effective Date set forth in the modified Privacy Policy. In all cases, your continued use of the Service or Website after the posting of any modified Privacy Policy indicates your acceptance of the modified Privacy Policy.

## Children

Our Service is not intended for children under the age of 13 (16 in the EU), and therefore, Sympli does not knowingly acquire or receive Personal Data from children under the age of 13 (16 in the EU). If we later learn that any user of our Service is under the age of 13 (16 in the EU), we will take appropriate steps to remove that user’s information from our account database and will restrict that individual from future access to the Service.

## Questions Regarding Personal Data

Please contact us if you have any questions or comments about our privacy practices or this Privacy Policy. You can reach us online at privacy@sympli.io, or by mail at:

Sympli, LLC   
Attention: Privacy Officer  
1211 31st Street, NW  
Washington, DC 20007  
USA
